Thank you for watching!
Thank you for watching
Next Episode Trailer
Music
Illustration
Movie
fill
Illustration
M לא
song
Spassion
Hello Hello Hello
Hello Hello Hello I want to touch you
Watarirulla must have jumped out of my hand.
Watarilla loves Ataka
Watarilla loves Ataka.
I don't know what's next
With a budding premonition
I want to shake the sad distance
I'm repeating my eyelashes laughing at you
Ah-
You and the sun shining through the trees
You know, you know, you know, you know
You know, you know, you know
You know, you know, light
You know, you know, close course
One time love, eh! I wish I could make that happen
Wondering Love, you and the clover I found
Garakuten
Inhale and write out the scenario
Transparent love, seduction blurring and floating in the air
Ah ah ah ah
Wonder little love
Hello Hello Hello Hello Hello
You know You know You know You know
Wonder little love
Wonder little love, just like saving the no-kill stream
Tiny Heart, where the excitement turns into rhythm
Wanderlust, you've jumped out of fantasy land
Wanderlust, no one knows what's ahead yet
In the season of new birth, a flower of precious grains
I drew even my pinky finger, wishing for bliss
Ha ha ha Wanderlust
Ranririrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr.
Yes, I am Yukina.
Yes, I am Chino Sora.
Yes, I am Director Murahoshi.
We are Uruka. Pleased to meet you.
Yes, so today is the release date of URUKA Major's 1st single
Wonder Little Love release date!
Yay!
Yes, this is the first time I've been to this venue since my youth novel.
Are you all fired up today?
Oh!
It's looking good.
So, today's Wonder Little Love
It's now No. 3 on the Oricon Daily Ranking!
Yay!
That's great!
I'm so happy!
Thank you so much!
Thank you all!
I couldn't have done it without all the pre-orders and purchases!
Thank you so much!
By the way, I'm at No. 3,
It was already No. 3 in the Oricon Weekly Ranking,
Oricon Weekly Ranking was No.5.
It started today, didn't it?
The week starts today.
It started today.
It has started, so I hope to reach No. 5 or even higher.
Aiming for No. 1?
First place.
First place?
This is first place.
I'm aiming for first place, so please do everyone a favor,
Please help us by spreading the word.
Please spread the word.
Also, we'll be distributing today.
That's right.
We'll also be streaming on YouTube.
Is it in the middle?
Where? In the middle?Where? In the middle?
Uh, in the middle.
Is that it?
Good evening, ladies and gentlemen.
Good evening.
Uka's official YouTube channel.
That's right.
YouTube channel.
Thank you very much.
Have a good time.
I'll see you soon.
Thank you very much.
We've got a lot going on today.
I have to go early.
Can I go next time?
Oh, yeah?
Yeah, sure.
Yeah? Today.
Yes, it is.
You didn't know?
Yes, I did.
All right, well, let's go.
Hold on.
What?
Are you kidding me?
You said you were going.
Yes, I'm sorry. Let's go, then.
Okay, listen up.
Tail window.
And I'm slowly clutching my back.
And I'm slowly clutching my back
Half an hour earlier than before
The alarm that fades down
The pippin of the heel of my hard-to-fit shoes
The unfamiliar subway
Sliding world affairs
It's my first time in bed
Anticipation and anxiety pound on the window
A continuation of the promise we made in class.
Safie, a long answer
I was pushed out of the room Brand New Day
We chose our paths a little differently
But I don't want to forget
I don't want to forget that we still feel the same way
I'm sure you're watching the fluttering petals
I'm sure you're watching too
In this place that still has no name
It's nice to meet you
I wonder if we'll get along
You're not good at smiling
I think so.
How could I smile?
Dreaming and spells
Time is our ant
Hey We'll be fine
Brand New Day, we're running through like we're being pushed out
We're going down an uncharted road Even though we're running and pushing But not yet
I want to take you to any scenery
The stars are falling and love is quickly fading away
Someday I wish
Love is here
The wind that blows through endurance
Let's dance with the new season
Though the path we chose was a little different
I'll always be on your side
Hang on, hang on, hang on, hang on
When you're feeling lonely
I'll tell you a story that's been on my mind
Tell me your story
Our wish is to tell you
A story that still has no name
[Applause]
Andere.
Yes, sir.
RAR
Gathering Galaxy
Flash Flash Citron
Flash Flash Float
Fly for you I dreamed of romance
Shake Shake Shake Shake
Shake Shake Shake Melt it down
Fantasy rear around marble
Dark glowing tones
I'll pop out with the smell
Hidden in a snooze
Symphony, I want to catch it
Banerava
Sometimes flowy
Sha-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la
One more time
Shalalaalaalaalaalaalaalaalaalaalaalaalaalaalaalaalaalaalaalaalaalaalaalaalaalaalaala
Swing Swing Swing Yeah
Swing Swing Swing Swing Swing
Shalalaalaalaalaalaalaalaalaalaalaalaalaalaalaalaalaalaalaalaalaalaalaalaalaalaalaala
Vaguely Yurusayasai Kimi
Even a cup of wind In a cider-blue star
Born of love, let's scatter in Najo tonight
Lush, Lush, Lush, Lush, Lush, Lush, Lush, Lush, Lush, Lush, Lush
Feel the blue oh
Sri Sri's sky, let me see through itIf you look through the sky of Sri Sri
Shake! Shake! Shake! Wish and
Shake Shake Shake Shake Shake Shake Shake Shake Shake Shake Shake Shake Shake Shake Shake Shake
The world will take your hand and start dancing
Twilight, to the toe-tapping
Someone else's love and melody
In the image that bloomed in the blink of an eye
Rain in the blink of an eye
Planet Love
Swing, Swing, Swing, Yeah!
Dazzling melody is now a signal
Comets are scattered all over the place, playing with the shimmering lights
Panel Love
Ah you and this place
Promise me, promise me
Shalalala...
Swing swing swing yeah
Vague timing
Thank you for watching
Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Yeah Yeah Yeah
Aren't you worried?
You've been alone all along, haven't you?
Aren't you stubborn?
If you love me, show me you're ready to give it to me softly!
Just a little forward
Just step out of the way?
Who are you looking at?
With words of dexterity
I want you to deliver it to me.
June love is light blue
tomorrow's curtains will be shining
I'll open the curtains of tomorrow
follow me
fluffy towels on your face
I'll share this much sun with you
that's what we're doing right now, right now
Don't worry about being able to fly
Is that not enough for you?
I can be hotter and stronger than ever
Without you
I'm not alone
Everything is in black and white
Maybe it's just easier to shake it all off
Carbon any day of the week
I just want to spray it down
I just wanna dance
♪ The stars in the sky are silent
I'm waiting for a sparkling tomorrow
I can't keep my fingers off the trigger, my heart rate's racing
Calling out to me
October bounces on the sea lamp
My wavy bangs swaying in the wind
It's on a timer, it's on a timer, it's on a timer, it'll be soon
Trust that I can fly
Without you
I have to be alone
Everything's in black and white.
Love Rain, kick it in the ass, break it down, tell a story
♪ Shine on, deep in my chest ♪ Aim, reach out, reach out, reach out
Again and again, again and again, get up, sing a song, raise your voice
Dive in, love is light blue, shimmering curtains of tomorrow
Open up the curtains of tomorrow, take a deep breath, don't panic, chase after it
I'll share with you the fluffy towel, I'll put my face in it, I'll ride the freshly risen sun
I'll share with you, now that we're all together, we're gonna go above and beyond, you'll notice
Trust me, break it down, break the story
♪ Shine on, deep in your heart, reach for it, reach for it, reach for it, reach for it, reach for it, reach for it.
Again and again, again and again, get up
Sing it, raise your voice, shout it
Hey... again, and again, and again
Hey... scream it again, and again, and again
Hey... again and again and again
Thank you very much.
Yes, sir.
That's what I'm talking about.
Normally, this is the last song.
I'm going to play one song.
But here...
It's still the same song.
The song will remain the same.
I'd like to do a project here
Oh!
What the hell?
What's the comparison?
Can you sing in the right rhythm?
Silent karaoke timing somehow.
This was a little difficult.
What the hell?
It's just that one time we did it.
It's just a normal recording of that song.
And then Killer Lips and Viva La Vida and 8:05.
And "8:05 Intersection" in that order.
The first time you listen to the original soundtrack.
And the second time, only a part of the song is played.
The second time, they played the silent part of the song.
And then we sang together.
If the sound and the song come together, the game is a success.
That's right.
Did you get it?
I remembered the title.Wait, I just remembered the title.
Just Timing.
Silent Karaoke Just Timing
Wow, that didn't go so well.
But I think I got the message.
I'll get right to it.
The soundtrack to Killer Lips.
Let's start with the karaoke.
Yeah, let's start with karaoke.
We're moving on now.
What? No?
I just explained that it's karaoke.
I'm sorry.
It's just... It's so confusing.
Let's do this one first.
Don't worry, we'll start from here.
Can you play the Killer Lips first?
I'll do the dance.
Let's get the timing down.
Chorus, chorus, chorus.
Two choruses, two choruses, two choruses, two choruses.
Two choruses?
Miyachan, here.
The part after the humph after the humph after the humph.
Ahhh...
2 choruses?
Isn't that the rhythm of the second chorus? And then...
Is it right?
Oh, I'm waiting.
There it is.
Is that it? Is that it?
You just said "kahn".
You just said "korn.
Dane.
Yeah, that was a while ago.
He was a shy boy.
Sora's part?
Shy boy.
Here's Sora's part.
Right there, where they overlap.
Okay, okay, okay.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Don't hide.
Yes, yes, yes.
Please.
First, the confidence tip.
Please have a voice.
Straight for you.
Like clockwork
I'm in love with you
Glittering lips
Why is that?
Just by closing my eyes and thinking
That melody running down my cheek
It's burning my heart
That melody that's burning my heart...
Yes, can you do it, member?
I'm nervous, I'm nervous.
Let's take it slow. Many times more than you think.
Do you want to take this outside?
Let's go outside.
This is a group competition, right?
Yes, it is.
First of all, our 247 is important.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
247, right?
It's fun, fun, fun!
What was that?
Oh, no, this way.
Let's go and try it.
Karaoke version?
We're on!
Kiralips, we're on! Let's start the music!
I'm a machine dream about you
24x7 No matter what I do, it won't go away
Glitter lips with heart arrows
Aimed straight at you
I'm a machine dream about you 24x7
Ichijun-o sax disasters
I can love you
I could love you
How can I love you?
very
strange and
very good
praise
first base
With you.
play
star
What do you think?
I got it.
But...
But it's too hard.
Why?
It was almost a circle.
It was almost a circle. I don't know what I should have done differently.
I'm serious, I'm serious, I'm serious.
You're a little early.
A little early. You were late.You're a little early. You're a little late.
You were late, you were late, you were late.
Too late, too late, too late, too late.
You're late, you're late, you're late, you're late, you're late, you're late, you're late, you're late.
Too fast? You were a little too slow on the breath-hold.
Too slow. Breath-hold, breath-hold. Breath-hold, breath-hold.
Okay, okay, okay.
That's the chorus for this moment, right?
Like that one. Okay, let's do it again.
Shall we do it again?
That's definitely not the same thing, right?
Revenge. Revenge?
Revenge? This one?
Revenge is okay. Revenge?
Yes! Yes!
Say that again in front of the reflection.
Because this time, next time, it'll be perfect.
You know, I heard a rumor...
There are three songs.
All three will be accepted.
All three? No, one at a time.
Oh, one song at a time? If you pass one song at a time...
You'll get a prize or something.
Wow, really?
Yes, so let's win!
Your eyes are burning.
Let's win. Okay, let's go, members.
Mr. House, would you like to go?
And now, for the second time, we will begin the Hilar Lips live soundtrack.
Yes, sir.
Chew! Chew! Chew!
24x7, no matter what I do, it won't go away.
♪ Twinkle, twinkle, twinkle ♪ ♪ With an arrow in my heart ♪
Aimed straight at you
Like clockwork
I'm in love with you
Thank you for watching.
What?
That's not good!
Well...
But sure, sure...
No, sure, sure...
Maybe 24 years old...
Maybe it's here.
No, wait, isn't that my clockwork problem?
Oh...
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no...
Well, I'll try the next one!
Next time!
Let's just go to the next one as a reminder!
Maybe next time it'll be harder!
That's right!
Right!
Next time is bad!
Next one's bad!
Next, next...
Vivala...
Viva La Viva?
Shall we go next?
Let's go!
I have no choice!
Next, I'd like to go to Viva la Vina!
See you later!
The real soundtrack!
The real sound!
Here we go!
Where are you?
The Super Adventures: The Story of the Chosen Brave Men
The Bearity prints that we all wanted to believe in.
Mass production is possible.
Crap is hard! Crap is hard!
Not at all!
Stop it! Stop it!
Hold on!
Wait a minute!
Get out of the way!
Hey!
Stop!
Up!
The hero is always Chubdan.
Yes, yes, yes.
Absolutely not! Never!
No! No! No! No, no, no, no, no!
No, no, no, no!
No, no, no, no, no!
- Okay. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
- Don't really clap anymore!
- No, the original.
- Oh, no! Oh, no!
- I can't do it anymore, I can't do it.
- If you can dance this, you'll never know.
- If it's a real click, I'd welcome it.
- Sure.
- It's fun.
- Yes, it would be fun.
- Let's go one time without claps.
- If it doesn't work, we'll get some help.- If we really can't, we'll get help.
- Right.
- Well, let's go live, shall we?
- A little early, maybe.
- But the voice?
- Double-headed?
- Double-headed.
- Double-headed. Where am I?
- Am I over here?
- I'm over here? - Oh, no.
- Oh, no,
- So, are you ready for the show, member?
- Okay.
- Let's go again.
- Okay, Viva La Beaver!
- Did you get it this way?
- I don't see it.
- I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry. You're almost right.
- Yeah, it's pretty much right, but Viva la Beaver, let's get to work!
It's all about opportunity.
Much more evolving sensation!
Hi!
Hard work, friendship, great adventure
The story of a chosen hero
Everyone wanted to believe
Rarity's Princeton Stall
Mass-produced mob characters.
Searching for love
Well, you can always continue again and again.
Ascending.
Ascend
The hero is always me.
Viva la vieja!
Yes!
Good, good, good!
Okay, this is Viva La Beadar.
Viva la beaver.
Um, what's the prize?
Is it in there?
This way!
Book cards! Book cards!
Book card! Book card!
Yay!
I'm so happy!
Shall we read a book?
Yeah, let's read a book.
Let's read a book? Here.
Is that it? He wants us to read books.
Dictionary, please buy another dictionary.
We can buy a dictionary.
We can buy an electronic dictionary.
Let's buy one for each of us.
Let's buy one.
Yes, thank you.
Yay, good, great!
That's great!
Yes, yes!
That's great. I wonder what's next.
Isn't the next one coming up?
It's not in the location.
It's definitely in the right place.
Okay, next intersection at 8:05.
Yes, sir.
Too long.
Hold on. Wait a minute.
Long.
This is number 2, isn't it? Let's have a listen.
Let's try it this way.
Okay, here's the actual recording of the second verse of "85 Minutes of Intersection.
Where's the first chorus?
It's not very loud, so I'll turn it up a little.
It's not very loud, so I'll turn it up a little bit.
It's not very loud, so I'm gonna turn it up a little bit
Percut out of uniform
Actually, it's 8:05 with matching watermelons
It's a stream of meaningless hearts
Vibration determined by deviation and AI
Please give me the words that I can't get unless it's now
Hey
QIJC I'm a girl too
You told me I was pretty even though I didn't have the courage
Many times already
I'm done.
Thank you very much.
- Hey. Right.
- Oh, thank you!
- Thank you!
- Finished?
- That was a piece of cake.
- It was a piece of cake.
- It was the easiest.
- It was the easiest. 85 minutes is the best.
- I wonder. I wonder what it is.
- I don't know.
- I think it's slow.- I think you're taking your time.
- I'll think about it.
- I think so.
- Is it difficult here?
- More and more, more and more.
- Yes, it is.
- Yes, it's slow, so it's scary.
- It might be the worst.
- That's not good.
- It's pretty long.
- From the percuts that stick out of the 2A uniforms.
- It's the longest one.
- It's "until...until...until...until...until...".
- I guess so. Can we go?
- Let's go for once.
- Let's go once.
- Let's go once more.
- Let's go take a look.
- Let's go take a look. Let's go take a look.
- Wait, wait. Where's this?
- From the time we go together.
- Let's get this 85-minute intersection underway!
Me.
A girl hates to lie.
But I want to be told I'm cute, so...
I've already told you how many times I love you, but I won't tell you
Only over the seasons
Beyond the contact
Today is the same as yesterday
perked up, sticking out of our uniforms, actually matching sneakers at 8:05
meaningless heart marks that flow out
Deviation values and the path decided by AI
Please give me the words I can only get now
Hey, Tintin Tintin
Q My Tenth
Me?
Because?
Over here?
Wow, that's subtle.
What about this one?
The other way, please.
What?
The screw-up competition?
A real man contest?
Let's see, let's see, let's see.
Is it "Magiman"?
What?
Yes!
Seriously?
Really? Really?
Tintin-tintin.
What? The judges are...
Yes!
Yeah! Yes!
I didn't expect that! I thought it was a little early.
A little bit.
So what's the prize for this song?
Can you pick one or the other? I choose!
What? Which one? I'd like to take a look.
You want to see it once? That doesn't make any sense.
You want to see it? It doesn't make sense.
Which do you want to see first?
You mean something or something?
Whoa!
Wait!
But the 10,000 yen one!
Oh, okay, okay, okay!
I'll give you the money too!
10,000 yen!
You can buy an iron!
I can buy a hair iron! I want to buy a hair curler!
Oh, no! It's too hot!
This is bad!
I don't have time for this! By the way!
Can we try Killer Lips again?
I have to!
I really want it!
I mean, you want it!
Come on! I'm ready!
I think I can make the show!
Okay?
Let's do it!
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Engine, engine!
Let's go!
Engine!
Come on!
Yeah!
Yeah, yeah!
Twenty-four!
Twenty-four?
Was I fast earlier?
You were late!
So, I was late.And now I've got it all over my head.
I'm covered!
Let's do it early!
I'll do it really fast too!
OK, OK!
I want to go to Campera!
This will be my last challenge!
Killer Lips start!
Mampachu to the Stars
24x7 No matter what I do, it won't go away.
Killer Lips Roof of hearts
I aim straight for you
Like clockwork, I'm in love with you
Kira Kira Lips
Oh, no.
No way.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Is that a new sound?
Yay!
Yes!
That means... that means..,
What does that mean?
Oh?
Yeah!
We did it!
We got three!
Yay!
Thank you so much.
Isn't that great? Isn't it great? Isn't that great?
I'm glad I got the best one.
I see. Thank you very much.
I'd like to take a break. We can't go on to the next song.
I can't go on to the next one.
I want to take a break. We can't go on to the next one.
Silent karaoke. I managed to get the timing right! Yay!
I succeeded. I forgot. It's okay, it's okay.
So, now that the fun karaoke is over, let's move on.
Next up... this way.
What is it?
We received your comments, so we'll play the song that everyone remembers from their youth.
We had a project for the "Seishun Shosetsu" (novel of youth), and we asked you what was your favorite song of your youth.
We were asking for your songs of your youth at Tower Records Akihabara store in Akihabara.
We've just been collecting the songs, and at this moment, we'd like to read out the songs that we've received from all of you.
Thank you very much for your patience.
It's so cute! It's so cute!
What do you think? What do you think?
What is the song of your youth? What is your favorite song of your youth?
I like MORE.
Some said, "I like Rina.
There are quite a lot of people who like it,
But among them, which one is it?
I found it just now.
By the way, who wrote it and who wrote it for me?
Youth music?
Oh, thank you very much.
Which one do you like?
Congratulations on your major label debut.
The song for youth is Kimi no na wa kibou. Mr. Kekoda.
Your name is hope?
Kimi no na wa, ah, Nagisaka-san, is it?
Nagiru, right?
Are you there?
He's not here today.
No, he's not here.
I forgot.
I see.
You're not here today.
I wonder if he's on QGM?
Thank you very much.
That's nice of you.
Who else is here?
Oh, no name.
But Suki-chan from Smileage.
Suki-chan.
That's nice.
She's cute.
After that...
The song for youth is Blue Hearts' "Be Kind to People" by Noue-san.
Be kind to others.
Are you there?
Yes, I'm here.
Thank you very much.
Blue Hearts.
And...
And, but, everyone is writing to congratulate you on your major label debut.
I'm very happy.
Thank you very much.
It's been over half a year.
I received it.
The song for youth is Yui's Cherry.
It rhymes, I think.
It rhymes.
Maybe, right?
Like high school.
This is your message.This your message.
And then there's the youth amigo.
Ancoween.
The drama.
This is Mr. Cordier, isn't it?
Thank you.
That's great.
Even after that, what it says is after-graffiti is Yukimo's.
It's youth, right?
Thank you.
I'm always happy.
Yes, it is.
It's nice.
There are a lot of songs.
Thank you very much.
I'll leave you to relax backstage later.
Thank you very much, everyone.
Well, I appreciate it.
Well, a lot of tsuntsuns came back. I'm so happy.
I wonder if there is no more time.
Well, maybe we can still go in the summer.
I wonder if I can still go.
What? Have you done something?
No, I mean...
I don't know... I'm just... I don't know...
I don't know.
But maybe not at all.
Oh, really?
You're sure?
I wonder what time it is.
What time is it?
I don't know what time it is.
It's taking a while.
It's 4:04. I can go another 15 minutes.
I can't. No, it's not. Should I go now? Five more minutes.
Five more minutes. Let's do the song we're going to lose. We're going to lose.
I don't like that. It's a little bit, it's release day. That's right. Sorry. Let's do it right.
Let's hear it. Now I would like to go to the last song. Let's go. This song was just released yesterday.
Yes, that's right. Now please listen to it. Growing Up Days.
Sleepless nights, I counted the stars, my heart's second hand shaking
I'm sorry, I'm anxious for tomorrow
Let's make a cup of tea and drink it
In the sky at 26 o'clock, I melted softly, softly, softly, softly
I pretended to be someone else someday, but I hid my true self.
Before I knew it, the smile we wanted to put on became better, and I didn't even realize I was hurting.
I wonder if I'll grow up to be a boring adult without realizing it.
Even though my days are full of obstacles, I'll walk the path just as I am.
I don't care if it's a clumsy way to live, I like the way I am now.
I gently and softly wrap up the feelings in my heart that are about to overflow
Raise the voice of my heart that I've been searching for, and become an adult
It's alright
When I cross the night, I'll open the wind and greet the new morning
Basking in the sun, nibbling on the lights, injecting vitamins into my heart
The sky at 8:00 a.m. is dancing, floating, floating, floating
Let the breeze blow softly, softly, softly
I'm so tired that I'm trying to be strong
Before you know it, all you've got are excuses
I can't be good at getting hurt
But I don't want to be a boring adult
I'll hold on to the pain in my heart
I'm ready to accept things as they are
I don't care if it's an uncool way to live
I still like me
I don't have to compare myself to anyone else
Because the time will come when I'll be an adult
Listen to the voice in your heart
I'm gonna grow up, I'm gonna grow up
I'm still a selfish soul
Hey, don't worry if I spoil you
Be strong
With me, your precious me, in every boring day
Say good-bye
Even if it's your everyday, let's walk like me
Even if it's a clumsy way to live, I like the way I am now
I'll gently wrap up the feelings in my heart that seem to overflow
Raise the heart and voice that you've been hiding and become an adult
It's alright
Thank you very much!
Yes, so Liz, please make an announcement.
Yes, the first major single "Wonder Little Love" was released today.
Wonder Little Love, which was released today, will have its final online special exhibition on the 23rd.
I will write my signature, Athena, the date, and a message on the clear file.
I will write a message on the clear file this time.
The deadline for reservations is 23:59 today.
Please make your reservation by 23:59 today.
Please make a reservation by 23:59 today.
We will have release events on the 24th in Hashimoto and the 25th in DiverCity.
On the last day of the event, the 25th, there will be a photo shooting time, so please come and have fun. Please come and visit us.
Please come and visit us.
So, everyone, today is the day of the release,
It is really thanks to all of you that we were able to release a major first single, and it is also thanks to Teichic Entertainment that we were able to release this single,
I would like to thank Teichic Entertainment for making it possible for us to release this major first single.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.Thank you very much.
We will do our best to move up a little higher in the weekly edition, so please continue to support us.
Thank you very much.
And to those of you who came even though it was a weekday, and to those of you who watched the broadcast, did you enjoy it?
Did you have fun?
It was fun!
I think it was fun.
It was a lot of fun.
We are looking forward to seeing you at the next release event on the 24th and 25th!
That's all for now.
Thank you very much.
- Good evening! Mr. Haneda! Mr. Wacky!
- Taggy!
- Good evening!
- Thank you very much!
- Thank you very much! Thank you in the back!
Thank you in the front too.
Thank you! Thank you in the back! Thank you in the front!
- Thank you!
- Thank you for YouTube!
Thank you very much!
- Bye bye!
Bye bye!
Thank you!
by H.
Subscribe to our channel